Daniel Schorr Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1933-2004 (Box 137-182)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 163)
    - Impeachment, 1974 (Box 163)
      - July-Aug., (3 folders) (Box 164)
    - Interview with Frank Gannon (1983), 2000, (2 folders) (Box 164)
    - Interview with Frank Gannon (1983), 2000, (6 folders) (Box 165)
    - Media, 1970-1977 (Box 166)
    - Miscellany, 1971-1977, 1992-1996 (Box 166)
    - Stone, Oliver, movie, 1995 (Box 166)
    - Tax investigation, 1969-1975, (2 folders) (Box 166)
  - North, Oliver L., 1986-1989, (3 folders) (Box 166)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1978, 1996-1997, (2 folders) (Box 166)
  - Nosenko, Yuri Ivanovich, 1964, 1980, 1991 (Box 167)
  - Nuclear energy, 1978-1979 (Box 167)
  - Organization of American States, 1991-1992 (Box 167)
  - Oswald, Lee Harvey, 1962-1964, 1973-1978, (3 folders) (Box 167)
  - Owen, Robert, 1984-1987 (Box 167)
  - Palestinian Liberation Organization, 1988 (Box 167)
  - Paley, William S., 1971-1980, (2 folders) (Box 167)
  - Parochial schools, 1971-1974 (Box 167)
  - Patman, Wright, 1972-1976 (Box 168)
  - Poindexter, John M., 1986-1987, (3 folders) (Box 168)
  - Poland, 1958-1959, 1979-1983 (Box 168)
  - Pollard, Jonathan Jay, 1998 (Box 168)
  - Pollution, 1969-1974 (Box 168)
  - Pordzik, Wolfgang, 1996 (Box 168)
  - Postal service, 1962-1977 (Box 169)
  - Poverty, 1967-1973, 1982-1984, (2 folders) (Box 169)
  - Powell, Colin L., circa 1995 (Box 169)
  - Presidential pardons, 1987-1996 (Box 169)
  - Prouty, L. Fletcher, 1969-1978 (Box 169)
  - Radio Free Europe/Voice of America, 1977-1980 (Box 169)
  - Reagan, Ronald (Box 169)
    - 1975-1980 (Box 169)
    - 1982-1984, (8 folders) (Box 170)
    - 1985-1999, (4 folders) (Box 171)
  - Religion, 1984 (Box 171)
  - Richard M. Nixon Library and Birthplace, Yorba Linda, Calif., 1992-1994 (Box 171)
  - Richardson, Elliot L., 1970 (Box 171)
  - Robinette, Glenn, 1984-1987 (Box 171)
  - Robinson, Robert, 1987-1990 (Box 171)
  - Rodriguez, Felix, 1987 (Box 172)
  - Romania, 1964-1969 (Box 172)
  - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1969 (Box 172)
  - Sachs, Albie, undated (Box 172)
  - Salant, Richard S., 1971-1979, 1995 (Box 172)
  - SALT II, 1978-1980 (Box 172)
  - Schevitz, Jeffrey, 1994-1995 (Box 172)
  - Schultz, George P., 1984-1987 (Box 172)
  - Schwartz, Abba, 1966 (Box 172)
  - Sciaroni, Bretton G., undated (Box 172)
  - Secord, Richard V., 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 172)
  - Secrecy, 1972-1983, (2 folders) (Box 172)
  - Segretti, Donald H., 1972-1973 (Box 173)
  - Shriver, Sargent, 1966-1967 (Box 173)
  - Sinatra, Frank, 1979 (Box 173)
  - Singlaub, John K., 1987 (Box 173)
  - Smallpox, 1984-1999 (Box 173)
  - Social security, 1978-1982 (Box 173)
  - Sofaer, Abraham D., 1987 (Box 173)
  - Sorensen, Theodore C., 1977 (Box 173)
  - Soviet Union (Box 173)
    - Education, 1955-1956 (Box 173)
    - Humor, 1986-1987 (Box 173)
    - Komitet Gosudarstvennoi Bezopasnosti (KGB), 1992-1997 (Box 173)
    - Media, 1985-1988 (Box 173)
    - Miscellany, 1955-1960, 1978-1988, (2 folders) (Box 173)
    - Ruble War, 1958 (Box 173)
  - Sporkin, Stanley, 1981-1987 (Box 174)
  - Stalin, Joseph, 1956 (Box 174)
  - Stanton, Frank, 1971-1977 (Box 174)
  - Strachan, Gordon, 1998-1999 (Box 174)
  - Sudan, 1996 (Box 174)
  - Tambs, Lewis A., 1986-1987 (Box 174)
  - Television and other media (Box 174)
    - Children, 1971-1986, (2 folders) (Box 174)
    - Courtrooms, 1977-1981 (Box 174)
    - Docudramas, 1971-1986, (3 folders) (Box 174)
    - Elections, 1980-1984 (Box 175)
    - Ethics, 1981-1984 (Box 175)
    - Fairness doctrine, 1986-1987 (Box 175)
    - Health, 1977-1981 (Box 175)
    - International communication, 1977-1982 (Box 175)
    - Miscellany, 1974-1982, (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Network mergers, 1977-1987, (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Newscasting, 1975-1981, (2 folders) (Box 176)
    - Politics, 1976-1982 (Box 176)
    - Public broadcasting networks, 1977-1979, 1986 (Box 176)
    - Public opinion, 1974-1985R (Box 176)
    - Regulation, 1974-1978 (Box 176)
    - Terrorism, 1976-1990 (Box 176)
    - United States Congress, 1975-1978 (Box 176)
    - Violence, 1969-1986, (3 folders) (Box 177)
    - White House, 1974-1985 (Box 177)
  - Thalidomide, 1979, 1997-1998 (Box 177)
  - Thornburgh, Richard B., 1990 (Box 177)
  - Toxins, 1975-1977 (Box 177)
  - Trigon, 1980 (Box 177)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1998 (Box 177)
  - Unidentified flying objects, 1997 (Box 177)
  - United States House of Representatives (Box 177)
    - Select Committee on Assassinations, 1975-1980, (3 folders) (Box 177)
    - Select Committee on Intelligence, 1975-1976, (5 folders) (Box 178)
  - United States Information Agency, undated (Box 178)
  - United States Supreme Court, 1982-1983, 1998 (Box 178)
  - Urban renewal, 1967 (Box 178)
  - Vesco, Robert, 1980 (Box 179)
  - Walker family espionage ring, 1985-1986 (Box 179)
  - Warren Commission, 1963-1965, 1974-1976, (2 folders) (Box 179)
  - Washington, D.C., 1966-1968 (Box 179)
  - Watergate Affair (Box 179)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1970-1975, (3 folders) (Box 179)
    - Civil suits, 1972 (Box 179)
    - Congressional hearings, 1973-1974 (Box 179)
    - Cox, Archibald, 1972-1974, (2 folders) (Box 180)
    - Deep Throat, 1981, 1992-2001 (Box 180)
    - Impeachment proceedings, 1972-1974, (2 folders) (Box 180)
    - Indictments, 1972-1975 (Box 180)
    - Miscellany, 1972-1983, 1992-1994, (7 folders) (Box 181)
    - Press, 1969-1975 (Box 182)
    - Subpoenas, 1973-1974 (Box 182)
    - White House tapes, 1972-1973, 1990-2003, (2 folders) (Box 182)
  - Watts community, Los Angeles, Calif., 1966 (Box 182)
  - Weinberger, Caspar W., 1985 (Box 182)
  - Welch, Richard S., 1976 (Box 182)
  - Whistle blowers, 1978, 1996 (Box 182)
  - Yugoslavia, 1965 (Box 182)
  - Zappa, Frank, 1986-1994 (Box 182)
- Miscellany, 1960-1994 (Box 182-183)
  Contract, legal case material, playing cards, and press passes.
  - Contract with assistant, 1979 (Box 182)
  - Court cases (Box 182)
    - Buchanan v. Cronkite, 1974 (Box 182)
    - Buendorf v. National Public Radio, 1990-1994, (3 folders) (Box 183)
    - Cramlet v. Multimedia Program Productions, 1982 (Box 183)
    - Dean v. St. Martin's Press, 1992-1993 (Box 183)
    - United States v. American Broadcasting Companies, 1974 (Box 183)
  - National Public Radio playing cards, undated (Box 183)
  - Press passes, 1960-1966 (Box 183)
- 2017 Addition, 1939-2010 (Box 184-194)
  Broadcast scripts, clippings, correspondence, articles and book production material, speeches, interviews, notes, and printed material.
  - Broadcasts and film (Box 184)
    - Cable News Network, 1981-1985 (Box 184)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1957-1964 (Box 184)
    - Discovery Channel, Watergate (documentary), circa 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 184)
    - National Public Radio scripts (Box 184)
      - 1985-1987, (4 folders) (Box 184)
      - 1987-1988, (9 folders) (Box 185)
      - 1989-1991, (8 folders) (Box 186)
      - 1993-2002 May, (8 folders) (Box 187)
      - 2002 June - 2002 Dec., (10 folders) (Box 188)
      - 2003-2006, (10 folders) (Box 189)
      - 2007-2010, undated, (7 folders) (Box 190)
    - Public Broadcasting System, 1996 (Box 190)
  - Correspondence (Box 190)
    - 1952, 1964-1999, (3 folders) (Box 190)
    - 2000-2009, undated, (1 folder) (Box 191)
  - Family and personal file (Box 191)
    - Biographical material, 1986, 1997-1999, undated (Box 191)
    - Clippings, 1939, 1956-2007, (5 folders) (Box 191)
    - Foreign Press Association of Netherlands, anniversary publication, 2005 (Box 191)
    - Miscellany, 1988, 2006, undated (Box 191)
    - Photograph, circa 1960s (Box 191)
    - Political cartoons, 1970-1976, 2007 (Box 191)
  - Miscellany (Box 191)
    - "Enemies list," circa 1973 (Box 191)
    - Notes, undated (Box 191)
    - Other journalists, circa 1990 (Box 191)
    - Reagan administration, information leaks, circa 1983 (Box 191)
    - Senate Select Committee on Intelligence report regarding Iran-Contra Affair, 1987 Jan. 29 (Box 191)
    - Statement, "Hearing on Crime and Violence in the Media," 1983 Apr. 13 (Box 191)
  - Speeches and public appearances (Box 191)
  - 1979-1994, (1 folder) (Box 191)
  - 1996-2010, undated, (2 folders) (Box 192)
  - Writings File (Box 192)
    - Articles (Box 192)
      - Atlanta Journal and Constitution, 1985-1989 (Box 192)
      - Christian Science Monitor, 1986-2006, (2 folders) (Box 192)
      - Los Angeles Times, 1983-1999 (Box 192)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 192)
        - 1952-2007, (4 folders) (Box 192)
        - Undated, (1 folder) (Box 193)
      - New Leader, 1967-1984, 1999-2009, undated, (6 folders) (Box 193)
      - New York Times, 1975-1998 (Box 193)
      - Progressive, 1974-1986 (Box 193)
      - Village Voice (Pike Papers report), 1976 Feb. (Box 193)
      - Washington Post, 1979-2005 (Box 193)
    - Books (Box 194)
      - Come to Think of It: Notes on the Turn of the Millennium foreward, circa 2006 (Box 194)
      - Staying Tuned: A Life in Journalism manuscript, 1998-2001, (2 folders) (Box 194)
- Oversize, 1926-2001 (Box OV 1-OV 3)
  Awards, certificates, posters, and miscellaneous news articles.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Family and Personal File (Box OV 1)
    - Awards and certificates
      - 1926-1930, 1978, 1980, 1988, 1994, undated (Container 1)
  - Speeches and Public Appearances (Box OV 2)
    - 1973
      - Poster, 1973 (Container 94)
    - 1987
      - Poster, 1987 (Container 102)
    - 1988
      - Poster, 1988 (Container 102)
    - 1998
      - Poster, 1998 (Container 111)
    - 2001
      - Poster, 2001 (Container 112)
  - Writings File (Box OV 3)
    - Articles
      - Miscellany, 1934-1948 (Container 122)